Guide to the L. Jackson Newell Audio-Visual Collection 1964-2012
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- University of Utah Hinckley Institute of Politics-L.Jackson Newell, undated; VHS videocassette 28 mins (Cassette 197)
- California Connect Show No. 309, 06 May 2004; VHS videocassette (Cassette 198)
  Air dates slated.
- Jack Newell Q and A Session, 01 October 1990; VHS videocassette (Cassette 199)
- University Professor Forum II: L. Jackson Newell, John Thelin, and Barbara Leigh Smith, 19 February 1992; VHS videocassette (Cassette 200)
- Jack's Interview at the Hinckley Institute with Ted Wilson as Moderator, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 201)
- MHA-1997-Omaha, VHS videocassette (Cassette 202)
  Leonard Arrington Luncheon and Sunday morning devotional
- Art as Education, 30 January 1990; VHS videocassette (Cassette 203)
- Fawn Brodie Symposium: No Man Knows My History-A 50-year Perspective, 09 August 1990; Audiocassette (Cassette 204)
  The 50th Anniversary of Fawn McKay Brodie's book-No Man Knows My History: The Life of Joseph Smith.
- Ballet Showcase II(01/27/2007)-Distracted Desire and Ballet Showcase II(01/25/2008)-Bound, 27 January 2007; 25 January 2008; DVD (Disc 205)
  Choreographed by Sayoko Knode
- Skating Bow Lake, Jennifer's First Steps, Jack and His Kids, December 1970; Super 8mm film (Reel 206)
- Ohawa, July 1973; Super 8mm film (Reel 207)
- Jennifer's First Birthday, December 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 208)
- Ranch, 1971; Super 8mm film (Reel 209)
- Jack's 31st Birthday, Lobster Dinner, and Jennifer's 1st Birthday, 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 210)
- Christmas(1968), Dinner at Fosters', and Jennifer as a Newborn, December 1968; Super 8mm film (Reel 211)
- Christmas(1968), Big Northeastern at Bow Lake, New Year's Even with Ellsworths and Gees, December 1968-January 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 212)
- Dad's Birthday Picnic, 1973; Super 8mm film (Reel 213)
- St. Louis Newells: Chris, Jen, and Eric, 1974; Super 8mm film (Reel 214)
- Christine's 4th Birthday, Dad Newell and Permafrost, and Folks Leaving Bow Lake, March 1970; Super 8mm film (Reel 215)
- Christmas(1970), Jennifer's 2nd Birthday, Moving from Bow Lake, February 1970; Super 8mm film (Reel 216)
- Jack's PhD Graduation, Aunt Louise's Party, September 1973; Super 8mm film (Reel 217)
- Chris's 5th Birthday, May 1971; Super 8mm film (Reel 218)
- Mt. Washington, Berlin, NH, Sharon, VT, June 1970; Super 8mm film (Reel 219)
- Eric and Family, 20 February 1973; Super 8mm film (Reel 220)
- Eric's First Birthday, Jan's Wedding, 18 March 1974; Super 8mm film (Reel 221)
- Nutz Knob, 1973; Super 8mm film (Reel 222)
- Dad's King and Granite Hill, undated; Super 8mm film (Reel 223)
- Untitled, undated; Super 8mm film (Reel 224)
- Christmas(1969-Dayton), Jennifer and Spaghetti, December 1969-January 1970; Super 8mm film (Reel 225)
- Untitled, 1979; Super 8mm film (Reel 226)
- Nutz Knob, 1979; Super 8mm film (Reel 227)
- Garden, Abby Horse, Fair Dearfiled, 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 228)
- Newell's etc. Ranch, June 1974; Super 8mm film (Reel 229)
- Ranch Trip, Dayton, St. Louis, CO, August 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 230)
- Bow Lake Garden, Penner's Camping, Moon Blastoff, NH, June 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 231)
- Ranch, Linda's Family, BCD Forest, Colo-Calif, August 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 232)
- Canoeing, 1974; Super 8mm film (Reel 233)
- Ranch, June 1974; Super 8mm film (Reel 234)
- Colorado Ranch, August 1969; Super 8mm film (Reel 235)
- Snow and Easter Basket, Booster Shots, April 1968; Super 8mm film (Reel 236)
- Deep Springs-A Desert Education, undated; VHS videocassette 103 mins (Cassette 237)
  A film by Christof Bove
- Deep Springs-A Desert Education, 0000; VHS videocassette 103 mins (Cassette 238)
- Julius Caesar at Deep Springs, 24 April 1999; VHS videocassette (Cassette 239)
  The cast consists of students, faculty and staff of Deep Springs. Directed by Louis Fantasia.
- Market to Market 2245, 25 July 1997; VHS videocassette 28 mins (Cassette 240)
  Deep Springs College
- Jennifer in East High Commercial, Deep Springs on Today Show, Deep Springs on Judy Hallet(SLC), Jack on Civic Dialogue, 13 September 1988; VHS videocassette (Cassette 241)
- Deep Springs College-Three Documentary Videos from CBS News Sunday Morning, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 242)
  Iowa Public Television, Ron Alexander, DS '64
- Deep Springs College-Three Documentary Videos from CBS News Sunday Morning, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 243)
- Deep Springs, Spring 1983 and Floods of Utah 1983, VHS videocassette (Cassette 244)
- Building Deep Springs with Jack Newell, 02 October 2004; VHS videocassette 41 mins (Cassette 245)
- October in Valley, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 246)
  Deep Spring History 1917-1950s
- Sunday Morning-Deep Spring College, 19 April 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 247)
- Deep Springs 1930s, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 248)
  16mm film shot by Buzz Anderson
- Deep Springs College Viewing Copy, undated; VHS videocassette 27 mins (Cassette 249)
- Market to Market 2245, 25 July 1997; VHS videocassette 28 mins (Cassette 250)
- Sunday Morning-Deep Spring College, 19 April 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 251)
- Rebuilding Deep Springs-A Tour with Linda Newell(Revised Version), 02 January 2005; VHS videocassette (Cassette 252)
- Deep Springs(1944-1945), 0000; VHS videocassette (Cassette 253)
- Deep Springs Pkg, 13 June 1985; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 254)
- Deep Springs-A Desert Education, undated; VHS videocassette 103 mins (Cassette 255)
- Deep Springs, undated; Compact disc (Disc 256)
  WDR and DLR, Public Radio Germany
- 58 TASP, 0000; Compact disc (Disc 257)
- Deep Springs Co-Education: Disk 1, undated; Compact disc (Disc 258)
- Deep Springs Co-Education: Disk 2, undated; Compact disc (Disc 259)
- Deep Springs Co-Education: Disk 3, undated; Compact disc (Disc 260)
- Deep Springs Co-Education: Disk 4, undated; Compact disc (Disc 261)
- Deep Springs Co-Education: Disk 5, undated; Compact disc (Disc 262)
- Building Deep Springs with Jack NEwell, 2004; DVD (Disc 263)
- Rebuilding Deep Springs Presented by Linda Newell, 2004; DVD (Disc 264)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 09 April 2005; CD 56 mins (Disc 265)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 14 April 2005; CD 54 mins (Disc 266)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 18 April 2005; CD 47 mins (Disc 267)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 18 April 2005; CD 46 mins (Disc 268)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 20 April 2005; CD 78 mins (Disc 269)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 05 May 2005; CD 72 mins (Disc 270)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 31 May 2005; CD 47 mins (Disc 271)
- Deep Springs Oral History: Geoff and Iris Pope, 31 May 2005; CD 38 mins (Disc 272)
- DS Alumni(1940s and 1980s), undated; CD (Disc 273)
- Bob Gatje's Film of Deep Springs (1944-1946), undated; DVD (Disc 274)
- Bob Gatje's Film of Deep Springs (1944-1946), undated; DVD (Disc 275)
- Bob Gatje's Film of Deep Springs (1944-1946), undated; DVD (Disc 276)
- Deep Springs College 92nd Anniversary Reunion, undated; DVD 126 mins (Disc 277)
- Deep Springs College 92nd Anniversary Reunion, undated; DVD 143 mins (Disc 278)
- Deep Springs College 92nd Anniversary Reunion, undated; DVD 129 mins (Disc 279)
- Deep Springs College 92nd Anniversary Reunion, undated; DVD 126 mins (Disc 280)
- Deep Springs College 92nd Anniversary Reunion, undated; DVD 143 mins (Disc 281)
- Deep Springs College 92nd Anniversary Reunion, undated; DVD 129 mins (Disc 282)
- L.L. Nunn's Philosophy in Founding Deep Springs: Presentation by Jack Newell, 20 March 2010; DVD 81 mins (Disc 283)
- L.L. Nunn's Philosophy in Founding Deep Springs: Presentation by Jack Newell, 20 March 2010; DVD 81 mins (Disc 284)
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 285)
  State of College/DS Medal Robert Gatje
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 286)
  Co-Ed Discussion
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 287)
  The Future of Electricity After Fossil Fuels
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 288)
  Alumni Public Speaking
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 289)
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 290)
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 291)
- DSC Reunion(2011), DVD (Disc 292)
- Deep Springs Fifties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 293)
  History of DS in the 50s
- Deep Springs Fifties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 294)
  Self-Government Then and Now
- Deep Springs Fifties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 295)
  State of the College
- DS Sixties, 19 September 2008; DVD 82 mins (Disc 296)
  Presentation with Audience Questions
- Deep Springs Sixties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 297)
- Deep Springs Sixties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 298)
- Deep Springs Sixties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 299)
- Deep Springs College(1964-1967), DVD (Disc 300)
  18 photos from Ron Alexander
- Deep Springs Fifties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 301)
  History of Deep Springs in the 50s
- Deep Springs Fifties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 302)
- Deep Springs Fifties Reunion, October 2008; DVD (Disc 303)
- Deep Springs Seventies Reunion, May 2009; DVD (Disc 304)
  "State of the College" by David Neidorf and "Fundraising by David Welle
- Deep Springs Seventies Reunion, May 2009; DVD (Disc 305)
- Deep Springs Seventies Reunion, May 2009; DVD (Disc 306)
  Discussion of the Labor Program Now and in the 70s
- Deep Springs Seventies Reunion, May 2009; DVD (Disc 307)
- Goodbye, Farewell, and Good Luck, 26 June 2009; DVD (Disc 308)
  Les and Debbie Smith, Katie Peterson-Class of 2007
- Goodbye, Farewell, and Good Luck, 26 June 2009; DVD (Disc 309)
- 50s-60s-70s Deep Springs Decade Reunions, 05 September 2009; DVD 35 mins (Disc 310)
  Presented at the 92nd Anniversary Reunion
- 50s-60s-70s Deep Springs Decade Reunions, 05 September 2009; DVD 35 mins (Disc 311)
- Deep Springs-A Desert Education, undated; DVD 142 mins (Disc 312)
- Rebuilding Deep Springs-A Tour by Linda Newell, June 2004; DVD 46 mins (Disc 313)
- Building Deep Springs-A Construction History by Jack Newell, October 2004; DVD 42 mins (Disc 314)
- 2005 Deep Spring Reunion: "First Day" Stories, 02 September 2005; DVD 50 mins (Disc 315)
- Deep Springs-A Documentary Film by Rolf Grimstead, 1986; DVD 18 mins (Disc 316)
- Deep Springs College on "Market to Market", 25 July 2005; DVD 7 mins (Disc 317)
- Deep Springs Performing Arts Committee(DSPAC), 19 March 2005; DVD 78 mins (Disc 318)
- Deep Springs Solar Array Dedication, 25 March 2006; DVD 41 mins (Disc 319)
- Deep Springs Interviews, August and September 2005; DVD 39 mins (Disc 320)
  List of Interviewees
  Gay and Terry Spitz-mother and father of Derek Spitz
  John Sinnin
  Michael Stryker
  Eunice Whitney, wife of Simon Whitney
  Deep Springs Director 1942-1947
- 80s Decade Reunion, 29 May 2010; DVD 106 mins (Disc 321)
  1980s History of Deep Springs
- 80s Decade Reunion, 30 May 2010; DVD 108 mins (Disc 322)
  State of the College Today and Looking Ahead
- 80s Decade Reunion, 29 May 2010; DVD 106 mins (Disc 323)
- 80s Decade Reunion, 30 May 2010; DVD 108 mins (Disc 324)
- 40s Decade Reunion, 03 June 2010; DVD 101 mins (Disc 325)
  40s History and Lives of Service
- 40s Decade Reunion, 03 June 2010; DVD 83 mins (Disc 326)
  State of the College and Securing Deep Springs for the Future
- 40s Decade Reunion, 03 June 2010; DVD 101 mins (Disc 327)
- 40s Decade Reunion, 03 June 2010; DVD 83 mins (Disc 328)
- Deep Springs 70s Decade Reunion, 23 May 2009; DVD (Disc 329)
  Presentation on 70s History by Jack Newell
- Deep Springs 70s Decade Reunion, 24 May 2009; DVD (Disc 330)
  "State of College" by David Neidorf and "Fundraising by David Welle
- Deep Springs 70s Decade Reunion, 24 May 2009; DVD (Disc 331)
- Eastern Sierra News-Deep Spriongs College Goes Co-Ed, 08 February 2012; DVD (Disc 332)
- Eastern Sierra News-Deep Spriongs College Goes Co-Ed, 08 February 2012; DVD (Disc 333)
- 90s Decade Reunion, 03 September 2011; DVD (Disc 334)
  Sate of the College and Self Government
- 90s Decade Reunion, 03 September 2011; DVD (Disc 335)
- 90s Decade Reunion, 03 September 2011; DVD (Disc 336)
- Understanding and Treating Depression, 03 September 2011; DVD (Disc 337)
  Dr. Jason Kurland DSC Main Room
- Deep Springs' Recruiting and Fundraisin Video and Documents, circa 2007; DVD (Disc 338)
  Includes Newell's essay "Education Of the Students"
- Deep Springs College-A DVD About Deep Springs, undated; DVD (Disc 339)
- Deep Springs College-A DVD About Deep Springs, undated; DVD (Disc 340)
- Jack Newell-Deep Springs Interviews Transcripts, undated; Compact Disc (Disc 341)
- Jack Newell-Deep Springs Interviews Transcripts, undated; Compact Disc (Disc 342)
- Deep Springs Brochure from Andy Kim, 25 June 2002; Compact Disc (Disc 343)
- Deep Springs 70s Reunion, 23 May 2009; DVD (Disc 344)
- Deep Springs 70s Reunion, 24 May 2009; DVD (Disc 345)
- Deep Springs 70s Reunion, 25 May 2009; DVD (Disc 346)
- Deep Springs 90th Anniversary Reunion, 31 August 2007-02 September 2007; DVD (Disc 347)
  Six Segments
- Deep Springs Sixties Reunion, September 2008; DVD (Disc 348)
- Deep Springs Sixties Reunion, September 2008; DVD (Disc 349)
- Deep Springs Sixties Reunion, September 2008; DVD (Disc 350)
- Retirement Picnic For Deep Springs Ranch Manager, Geoff Pope(1981-2005), 03 June 2005; DVD 82 mins (Disc 351)
- Sound of the Southwest 8, undated; Audiocassette 35 mins (Cassette 352)
  L.L Nunn Alternating Current KOTO-fm, Telluride, CO
- Buzz Anderson DS39, 24 January 1989; Audiocassette (Cassette 353)
  Recorded 1/24/1989, Rerecorded 10/01/08
- Norton Dodge, DS Oral History Project, 31 January 1989; Audiocassette (Cassette 354)
  Re-recorded 10/01/08
- Ed Hoenicke, 10 October 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 355)
  Contais all the material recorded by Jack Newell with Ed Hoenicke
- Bonham Campbell Oral History, 13 September 1998; Audiocassette (Cassette 356)
- Ed Hoenicke Part 2, 10 October 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 357)
- Dedication of Henderson Station, 13 July 1996; Audiocassette (Cassette 358)
- L.J. Newell Ed Loomis Tape 2, 12 August 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 359)
- L.J. Newell David Schisgall, 30 June 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 360)
- L.J. Newell Ed Wesely Tape 2, 29 June 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 361)
- L.J. Newell Ed Loomis, 12 August 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 362)
- L.J. Newell Ed Wesely Tape 1, 29 June 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 363)
- Dr. Randall C. Reid Oral Interview, 12 March 1989; Audiocassette (Cassette 364)
  Dr. Randall C. Reid Deep Springs 1949. Tom Hudgens and Scott Fybush
- Unlabeled, undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 365)
- 90th Reunion-"First Day of School", 31 August 2007; Audiocassette (Cassette 366)
- 90th Reunion Deep Spring, Married to the Valley, Hydro and Solar History, 02 September 2007; Audiocassette (Cassette 367)
- 90th Reunion Deep Spring, Class of '57, 02 September 2007; Audiocassette (Cassette 368)
- 90th Reunion Deep Spring-Jack Newell "Deep Springs the Early Years", Married ot the Valley, 02 September 2007; Audiocassette (Cassette 369)
- 90th Reunion "Perspectives on Education", 01 September 2007; Audiocassette (Cassette 370)
- Swatek '33 and Laverty '43, undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 371)
- Wm J Vanden Heuvel, 05 October 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 372)
- Notes on Deep Spring Alumni by Fred Laise, undated7; Audiocassette (Cassette 373)
- Ed Hoenicke Personal Background, undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 374)
  DS Student 1946-48, DS President 1990-92
- Ed Hoenicke Interview, 10 October 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 375)
- Lindsey Grant DS 1943, 06 February 1989; Audiocassette (Cassette 376)
- Carlyle M. Ashley DS 17, 1988; Audiocassette (Cassette 377)
- DS 1950s Culture, 25 October 2008; Audiocassette (Cassette 378)
- Wm J Vanden Heuvel, 05 October 2006; Audiocassette (Cassette 379)
- L.L. Ninn, Pioneer, undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 380)
  KOTO FM Telluride, CO
- Dr. Randall C. Reid, 1989; Audiocassette 40 mins (Cassette 381)
- Lindsey Grant DS 1943, Oral History, 05 February 1985; Audiocassette (Cassette 382)
  Annex to 2/5/85 interview
- Bonham Campbell Oral History, 13 September 1998; Audiocassette (Cassette 383)
  DS Student 1931-34, Asst. Director 1946-48, Director 1948-51
- Farewell Speeches DS 98, June 2000; 8mm videocassette (Cassette 384)
- Slaughtering Beef, 25 April 1999; 8mm videocassette (Cassette 385)
- DS Life Fall 1997-1998, 8mm videocassette (Cassette 386)
- DS Fall 1999, 8mm videocassette (Cassette 387)
- Main Building Renovation, 1998-1999; 8mm videocassette (Cassette 388)
- Farewell Speeches Second Night, 1999; 8mm videocassette (Cassette 389)
- Farewell Speeches First Half, 1999; 8mm videocassette (Cassette 390)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 391)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 392)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 393)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 394)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 395)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 396)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 397)
- Unlabeled, undated; microcassette (Cassette 398)
- Matters of Conscience(Copy Edited Version), undated; floppy disc (Disc 399)
- Jack Newell's email back-up and address back-up, 19 April 2002; floppy disc (Disc 400)
- Publications-2002 Annual Report, Press Letter, 01 November 2002; floppy disc (Disc 401)